<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2023 Joe Da Silva <digital@joescat.com> -->
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.gimp.extension.fix-ca</id>
  <extends>org.gimp.GIMP</extends>
  <name>Fix Chromatic Aberration</name>
  <summary>[plug-in to correct Lateral or Directional Chromatic Aberration (CA)]</summary>
  <description>
    <p xml:lang="C">
    This extension helps the user correct Lateral Chromatic Aberration (CA) due
    to different color wavelengths travelling through a lens, or Directional CA,
    where the amount of CA is assumed to be the same throughout the image due to
    light travelling through dense material such as glass or water.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">
    Esta extensión ayuda a corregir la aberración cromática lateral (CA) debido
    a diferentes longitudes de onda de color que viajan a través de una lente,
    o CA direccional, donde se supone que la cantidad de CA es la misma en toda
    la imagen debido a luz viaja a través de materiales densos como vidrio o agua.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
    Cette extension aide à corriger l'aberration chromatique latérale (CA) due
    à différentes longueurs d'onde de couleur voyageant à travers une lentille,
    ou Directional CA, où la quantité de CA est supposée être la même dans toute
    l'image en raison de la lumière voyageant à travers un matériau dense comme
    le verre ou l’eau.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">
    Esta extensão ajuda corrigir a Aberração Cromática Lateral (CA) devido
    para diferentes comprimentos de onda de cores viajando através de uma lente,
    ou CA direcional, onde a quantidade de CA é considerada a mesma em toda a
    imagem devido a luz viajando através de materiais densos, como vidro ou água.
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/JoesCat/gimp-fix-ca</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/JoesCat/gimp-fix-ca#readme</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/JoesCat/gimp-fix-ca/issues</url>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <releases>
   <release version="4.0"   date="2024-02-24" />
   <release version="3.0.4" date="2023-12-02" />
   <release version="3.0.3" date="2022-10-09" />
  </releases>
  <requires>
   <id version="2.10" compare="ge">org.gimp.GIMP</id>
  </requires>
  <metadata>
   <value key="GIMP::plug-in-path">fix-ca</value>
  </metadata>
</component>
